<DialogueTree xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/dialogue_schema.xsd">
	<NameField>cOa Rex</NameField>


	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>INITIAL</Name>
		<EntryCondition>DEFAULT</EntryCondition>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Hey Traveler! They called me Rex, or cOa.</Page>
			<Page>I'm the drawer who worked on some mods like Cosmics Curators or Eyes of the Past.</Page>
			<Page>I'm also working on an animation like the DLC slide reels named A Stranger I Remain. It's also where come from the character "the Stranger".</Page>
			<Page>You know, sometimes, you have dreams or projects, like, big dreams. And more little dreams. But doesn't make them less important.</Page>
			<Page>One of mine was to do a mod and be on the team of Anon, pikpik, Stache, and Repcon. Well, my team actually.</Page>
			<Page>Live simple life can also means to enjoy every little dreams like this that coming true. And I have made a souvenir of our team. Maybe you will find it. It's pretty easy.</Page>
			<Page>You can find me on Discord by cOa Rex, on in Youtube by centre Ombre alpha. This is where I will upload A Stranger I Remain... When it will be ready.</Page>
			<Page>Feel free to come talk, or if your need 2D Arts for a mod or for something, maybe I could help, even if I take time for everything.</Page>
			<Page>Also, be sure to explore mods. The Stranger They Are, Forgotten Castaways, etc, etc. This is because people make mod, and people playing it, make feedback, and share that Outer Wilds continue to live.</Page>
			<Page>So, see you in Eyes of the Past, The Cosmic Curators, The Stranger They Are, and A Stranger I Remain.</Page>
			<Page>And maybe... in another story mod ? Yeah, that is my little secret for now, but I have a idea for it, even if it takes years, I hope you will still be there.</Page>
			<Page>Before that, I have a lot of things to learn, and to do. Because my imagination never stop!</Page>
			<Page>Have a nice exploration!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
		<DialogueOptionsList>
			<DialogueOption>
				<RequiredCondition>AnonPissed</RequiredCondition>
				<Text>What was that about Anon, again?</Text>
				<DialogueTarget>anon</DialogueTarget>
			</DialogueOption>
		</DialogueOptionsList>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode>
		<Name>anon</Name>
		<Dialogue>
			<Page>Oh yeah, Anon? They really don’t like the light, you know.</Page>
			<Page>You have to walk up to them without any lights on, or else they will just keep kicking you out, like, again and again.</Page>
			<Page>Once you done it the first time, it’s too late, my friend.</Page>
			<Page>You might have to restart to be able to talk to them again. It can be a bit annoying, but that is how it is!</Page>
		</Dialogue>
	</DialogueNode>
</DialogueTree>